<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_title_1">What is FP cashback?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1">In addition to the discounts you avail on online shopping that are available on FlyingPaisa, you
can get additional cashback on your online shopping. It is a kind of extra savings that you can
make from us. On every store page at FlyingPaisa, you can identify the additional cashback
available for a store by looking at the CASHBACK RATES table or by looking at Up To 5% FP
additional Cashback. To earn cashback please ensure that you get redirected to the store only
via the FlyingPaisa link and make your purchase. Once your transaction is done, cashback gets
tracked within 48 hours and is added to your pending balance. Due to return policy of the
product and validation process at retailers, it takes 4-10 weeks of time to get cashback in
confirmed state. Once we receive the final confirmation of the purchase from the retailer, we
confirm the cashback then pending balance made available for you to use. CCashback earned
from FlyingPaisa is your money and can be used to transfer into bank account, recharge your
phone/DTH, online wallet transfer and get online shopping vouchers.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_2">What are FP Rewards?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2">Some stores like Flipkart do not allow cashback earned from them to be transferred into bank
account. They can be redeemed for transfers to an online wallet like PayTM, Mobikwik,
freecharge, making a mobile phone or DTH recharge or getting shopping vouchers. To make
this distinction easier to understand, the cashback earned from these merchants is referred to
as FP Rewards. The process for earning of FP Rewards is the same as FP Cashback, and the
only distinction being that FP Rewards cannot be withdrawn to a bank account. It is due to this,
that the available balance on a bank transfer page may be less than your actual available
balance. Any stores carrying Rewards instead of Cashback will explicitly mention them on the
respective store pages. The majority of stores do not carry rewards.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_3">What is FP Voucher Cash?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3">When You Shop on Amazon, the Cashback Earned can be redeemed Only via Amazon
Vouchers. Thus the Cash earned on Amazon is Voucher Cash. It can be redeemed in form of
Amazon Vouchers/Gift Cards via FlyingPaisa which can be used to Shop on Amazon.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_4">What is the difference between pending and available balance?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4">Pending balance earned from purchases made at cashback stores usually requires 4-10 weeks
wait period before which it becomes available. This is because most stores wait until their return
and exchange period is over before confirming a purchase. If a merchant finds a purchase as
cancelled or exchanged, the pending balance does not become available and will be removed
from your account. Pending balance earned from promotional activity like referrals has its own
conditions that must be fulfilled for it to become available. Pending balance earned on referring
your friend will be confirmed once your friend will earn min of Rs 99 in his confirmed state.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_5">Why does FP cashback take so long to confirm?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_5">We have to wait for the store to confirm to us that the purchase was not returned or exchanged.
Merchants also use this time to validate that the sale has met conditions for earning of
cashback. We constantly work with stores to reduce this wait period. However, just to be on
good terms we inform you that it may usually take 4-10 weeks for a transaction to be confirmed.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_6">How does my pending balance become available balance?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_6">Pending balance earned from purchases made at cashback stores usually requires 4-10 weeks
wait period before which it becomes available. This is because most stores wait until their return
and exchange period is over before confirming a purchase. If a merchant finds a purchase as
cancelled or exchanged, the pending balance does not become available and will be removed
from your account. Pending balance earned from promotional activity like referrals has its own
conditions that must be fulfilled for it to become available. Pending balance earned on referring
your friend will be confirmed once your friend will earn min of Rs 99 in his confirmed state.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_7">There was an offer I saw but it no longer exists on the site. How can I get it?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_7">In some cases, the offers given to us by the store are only valid for a limited duration or until
promotion lasts. When the offer reaches its expiration date, we automatically remove it from our
Website and Apps. This is done to ensure that you have a great all around experience and do
not attempt to use offers which no longer work.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_8">How can I withdraw my balance?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_8">To withdraw your balance, log in to your FlyingPaisa account and visit the MyAccount section
>Transfers of your profile. Select the method of withdrawal, bank, e-wallet or recharge. Select
the account where you wish to transfer your Available Balance. Enter the amount and hit
Submit. Bank transfers take between 3-4 business days to reflect in your account. eWallet and
Recharge transactions are almost instantaneous but can take upto 48 hours to reflect in your
account.</string>

    <string name="faq_title_9">How do I check the status of my order?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_9">You can view the Status of Your Order by logging to your FlyingPaisa Account > Gift Card
Orders by using the unique reference number provided to you at the time of purchase.</string>

</resources>